Guide to the Lorin Edgar Kerr Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- United Mine Workers of America, 1948-1978; Series I; 9 linear feet (22 boxes)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    - Memorial General Hospital Association
      See also: box 4, Folder 60
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional Medical Program, 1967-1974 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Miller, Arnold R.(*), 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 102)
      See also: box 6, folder 103 See also: box 12, folders 192-202
    - Miller, C. Arden, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 102)
      See also: box 2, folders 19-29
    - Mills, Wilbur D., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Mine disasters
      See also: box 2, folder 26 See also: box 2, folder 31 See also: box 3, folder 55
    - Miners for Democracy, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Miners Loyalty Fund, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Moore, Raymond T.
    - Morgan, Keith C.
      See also: box 1, folder 16
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Muskie, Edmund S., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Myers, Beverlee A., 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Nae - Nav (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Ne - Nu (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 109-110)
    - National Conference on Medicine and the Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act of 1969, 1969, 1970 February-May (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - National Conference on Medicine and the Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act of 1969, 1970 June (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - National Conference on Medicine and the Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act of 1969, 1970 July-Dec, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 113-114)
    - National Heart and Lung Institute, 1969, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - National Rehabilitation Association, 1967-1973 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - National Research Council, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - National Transplant Information Center, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - National Tuberculosis and Respiratory Disease Association, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - National Voluntary Organizations, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Newdorp, John
      See also: box 11, folder 183 See also: box 11, folder 191 See also: box 12, folders 200-201
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - New York Academy of Sciences
      See also: box 8, folder 142
    - New York Academy of Sciences, Conference on Coal Workers' Pneumoconiosis, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - O (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Owens, John, 1969, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Pa - Pe (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Ph - Q (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Parker Film Association, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Patrick, Harry
      See also: box 12, folders 200-202
    - Pendergrass, Eugene, 1958, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Pennsylvania Bureau for the Aging, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Pennsylvania Lung Association, 1968, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Pennsylvania State University, Panel on Bituminous Coal Industry, 1972 December-1973 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Pennsylvania Tuberculosis and Health Society, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Pepper, Claude, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Potter, John F., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Public Health Reviews, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Ra - Ri (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Ro - Ry (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Rasmussen, Donald L.
      See also: box 2, folder 17
    - Reuther, Walter, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Roche, Josephine, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 134)
      See also: box 11, folder 183
    - Roemer, Milton, 1971-1974, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Roemer, Ruth (Mrs. Milton), 1974, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Rogan, John M., 1965-1974 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Rogers, Paul G., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Rogers (Will) Hospital, 1972 March-November (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Rosenfeld, Leonard S., 1967, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Sa - Sc (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Se - Sh (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Si - Sp (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - St - Sy (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Science World, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - The Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Selikoff, Irving J., 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Shoub, Earle P.
      See also: box 1, folder 16 See also: box 9, folder 160
    - Sinai, Nathan, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Southeastern Kentucky Regional Health Demonstration, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Stillman, Donald
      See also: box 11, folder 184 See also: box 12, folders 200-201
    - Student American Medical Association, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Sulka, John
      See also: box 12, folder 201
    - T (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Tabershaw, Irving R., 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Terris, Milton, 1967-1973, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 147)
      See also: box 8, folder 143
    - Trbovich, Mike
      See also: box 12, folders 200, 202
    - Trulos, Michael
      See also: box 12, folder 193
    - U (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Union Carbide Corporation, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - United States A - Z (Box 9, Folder 150)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1965-1978 (Box 9, Folder 151-158)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health, 1972-1978 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, National Institute of Mental Health Conference, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1969, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 161-162)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - United States Department of the Interior, 1968-1969, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - United States Executive Office of the President, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 164)
    - V (Box 10, Folder 165)
    - Van Goor, Robert E.
      See also: box 38, folder 225 See also: box 41, folders 264-265 See also: box 42, folder 274 See also: box 42, folder 276
    - Voorhis, Jerry, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 166)
      See also: box 37, folder 219 See also: box 38, folder 234
    - Wa - We (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - Wh - Wy (Box 10, Folder 168)
    - Wegman, Myron E., 1967-1974 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1969-1971 February-December (Box 10, Folder 170-175)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - White House Conference on Food, Nutrition, and Health, 1969 October-December (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - White House Conference on Health, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Williams, Harrison A., 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - Wilson, Glenn
      See also: box 38, folder 227 See also: box 38, folders 230 See also: box 38, folders 232 See also: box 41, folder 265
    - Witt, Bert, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Witt, Lauren, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Witt, Paul, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Wolfe, Sidney M.
      See also: box 2, folder 69
    - X, Y, Z (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - Yablonski, Joseph A.
      See also: box 12, folder 200-201
    - Interoffice Files
      See also: box 2, folder 27 box 6, folder 97 box 6, folder 102
      - Pamphlets and leaflet, 1957,1962, undated (Box 11, Folder 182)
      - General correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 183)
      - Correspondence re: journal, 1967-1973 (Box 11, Folder 184)
      - Correspondence and reports re: Medical Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 185)
      - Statements, 1969, undated (Box 11, Folder 186)
      - Press releases, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 187)
      - Miscellaneous clippings, 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 188)
      - General correspondence, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 189)
      - Correspondence and reports re: Medical Advisory Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 190)
      - Correspondence re: 1971 contract, 1971 October-November (Box 11, Folder 191)
      - Correspondence, schedules and lecture outline re: Staff Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 192)
      - General correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 193)
      - Correspondence and leaflets re: blood donor program, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 194)
      - Press releases, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 195)
      - Correspondence re: Research and Marketing Department, 1972 April-1973 (Box 12, Folder 196)
      - "Better Health Gems," United Mine Workers Journal, 1972 May-1973 (Box 12, Folder 197)
      - Miscellaneous lists and forms, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 198)
      - Posters, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 199)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 12, Folder 200-202)
  - Welfare and Retirement Fund
    - Statistical Reports, 1948 December-1949 May, 1949 August-December (Box 12, Folder 203-204)
    - Statistical Reports, 1950 July-1951 October (Box 13, Folder 205-207)
    - Hospital and Physicians' Service Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 208-209)
    - Hospital and Physicians' Service Reports, 1954-1956 June (Box 14, Folder 210-214)
    - Hospital and Physicians' Service Reports, 1956 July-1957 Sep, 1958-1959 June (Box 15, Folder 215-219)
    - Hospital and Physicians' Service Reports, 1959 July-Sep, 1951 December-1953 (Box 16, Folder 220-224)
    - Medical Care Statistics, 1954-1956 June (Box 17, Folder 225-229)
    - Medical Care Statistics, 1956 July-1958 (Box 18, Folder 230-234)
    - Medical Care Statistics, 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 235-239)
    - Medical Care Statistics, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 240-243)
    - Medical Care Statistics, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 244)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Services Reports, 1950-1956 (Box 21, Folder 245-249)
    - Miscellaneous Statistics, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 250-251)
- Other Professional Activities, 1944-1978; Series II; 10 linear feet (24 boxes)
  OTHER PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES is organized in six sections: American Public Health Association, District of Columbia Department of Public Health, Public Health Council, District of Columbia Public Health Association, Group Health Association of America, Howard University, and National Institute on Rehabilitation and Health Services. The larger sections are organized in subsections; each section or subsection is arranged chronologically.
  - American Public Health Association
    - General Papers
      - Correspondence and subject files
        - Policy statements, 1944-1946, 1951-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Committee and section lists, 1962-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Index of professional program, 1965 October (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Policy drafts and correspondence re: group insurance, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence and editorials, American Journal of Public Health, 1965-1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - Newsletters, 1968-1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence and speech texts re: annual meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - Testimonies and statements, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence and related material re: national health insurance, 1971 February-September (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, agenda and speech texts re: annual meeting, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - Directory and other member lists, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - Organization charts, 1971-1972, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence, speech drafts and background material re: annual meeting, 1972 July-November (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Questions and answers re: presidential campaign (A.P.H.A.), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence re: presidential campaign (A.P.H.A.), 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence, 1973 January-Nov, 1973 December (Box 24, Folder 19-20)
        - Correspondence and speech texts re: annual meeting, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 21)
        - Correspondence, press releases and related material re: Coalition for Health Funding, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 22)
        - Newsclippings and releases, 1973, 1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence, 1974 January-September (Box 24, Folder 24-27)
        - Correspondence, speech text and program re: annual meeting, 1974 October-November (Box 24, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence, 1974 October-December (Box 24, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence, 1975 May-December (Box 25, Folder 30-31)
        - Correspondence re: annual meeting, 1975 January-December (Box 25, Folder 32)
        - Speech texts re: annual meeting, 1975 November 17-19 (Box 25, Folder 33)
        - Audio recording, "Politics of Developing a National Occupational Health Policy", 1975 (Box 25, Folder 34)
        - Correspondence re: annual meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 35)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Executive Board
        - Agenda and background material, 1970 October 24-30, 1971 February 18-19, 1971 June 24-25 (Box 25, Folder 37-39)
        - Agenda and background material, 1972 February 24-25, 1972 June 15-16 (Box 26, Folder 40-41)
        - Background material for meeting, 1972 June 15-16 (Box 26, Folder 42)
        - Agenda, minutes and background material, 1972 September 20-22 (Box 26, Folder 43)
        - Agenda and background material, 1972 November 10-17, December 18-20 (Box 26, Folder 44)
        - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 45)
        - Agenda and background material, 1973 February 22-24 (Box 26, Folder 46)
        - Agenda and background material, 1973 May 3-4, September 13-14 (Box 27, Folder 47-48)
        - Background material for September meeting re: International Health Programs, 1973 September 13-14 (Box 27, Folder 49)
        - Agenda and background material, 1974 January 15 (Box 27, Folder 50)
        - Agenda and background material, part I, 1974 February 7-8 (Box 27, Folder 51)
        - Agenda and background material, part II, 1974 February 7-8 (Box 27, Folder 52)
        - Agenda and background material, 1974 May 2-3 (Box 27, Folder 53)
        - Agenda and background material, part I, 1974 August 8-9 (Box 28, Folder 54)
        - Agenda and background material, part II, 1974 August 8-9 (Box 28, Folder 55)
        - Agenda and background material, 1974 September 25, December 18 (Box 28, Folder 56-57)
        - Agenda (tentative) and background material, 1975 February 13-14 (Box 28, Folder 58)
        - Agenda and background material, 1975 March 26, May 15-16, June 26, August 20, September 10-12 (Box 28, Folder 59-63)
        - Background material, 1975 October 15 (Box 28, Folder 64)
        - Report draft and notes, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 65)
      - Governing Council: resolutions and list of members, 1959-1962, 1968-1973 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Committees and Sections
      - Action Board
        - Correspondence and minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 29, Folder 67)
        - Minutes and agenda, 1974 January-August (Box 29, Folder 68)
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1974 March-November (Box 29, Folder 69)
        - Reports, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 70)
        - Minutes and correspondence, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 71)
      - Awards Committee: list of members and nominees, correspondence and speech text, 1969-1981 (Box 29, Folder 72)
      - Committee on Affiliated Associations and Regional Branches
        - Reports, 1953, 1965-1966, n.d (Box 29, Folder 73)
        - State constitutions, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 74)
        - Memoranda, 1964-1967 (Box 29, Folder 75)
        - Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 29, Folder 76)
        - "Statement on Functions of National, Regional, State and Local Public Health Associations", 1965 January (Box 29, Folder 77)
        - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 78)
        - Pamphlet and working copy for Guide For Affiliated Associations and Regional Branches American Public Health Association, 1966, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 79)
        - Lists of members, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 80)
        - Memoranda, agenda and summary re: Task Force on Affiliates, 1967 March-April (Box 29, Folder 81)
        - Minutes, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 82)
        - Correspondence, memoranda and background material re: affiliates' presidents-elect meetings, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 83)
        - Memoranda, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 84)
        - Self-evaluation survey questionnaire and related material, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 85)
        - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 86)
        - Draft: Manual of Background Information on APHA for Secretaries of Affiliates, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 87)
        - Memoranda, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 88)
        - History re: Ad Hoc Committee on Chapters, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 89)
        - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 90)
        - Memoranda, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 91)
        - Report drafts, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 92)
        - Background material and notes re: Ad Hoc Committee on chapters, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 93)
        - Correspondence and memoranda re: Ad Hoc Committee on chapters, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 94)
        - Report, Ad Hoc Committee on Chapters, 1972 September 29 (Box 30, Folder 95)
        - Proceedings, 1972 October 6 (Box 30, Folder 96)
        - Conference on Association Functions, Organizations, and Relations (C.A.F.O.R.)
          - Background material re: First Arden House Conference, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 97)
          - Background material re: Second Arden House Conference, 1968 January-Dec, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 98-99)
          - Correspondence and memoranda re: Second Arden House Conference, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 100)
          - Report re: Second Arden House Conference, 1969 April 7-10 (Box 31, Folder 101)
          - Program outline, list of conferences re: Second Arden House Conference, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 102)
        - Conference of Affiliate Representatives on the Governing Council (A.R.G.C.): agenda, memoranda and outline, 1964-1970 (Box 31, Folder 103)
        - Southern branch: bulletin, constitution and bylaws, 1966, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 104)
        - Western branch: correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 105)
      - Constitution and Bylaws Committee: constitution and bylaws, 1961, 1970-1975 (Box 31, Folder 106)
      - Council on Education for Public Health: correspondence and memorandum, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 107)
      - Eligibility Committee: correspondence and reprints, 1961-1973, undated (Box 31, Folder 108)
      - Emergency Ad Hoc Committee on Chilean Health Workers
        - Correspondence and memoranda re: Chilean health workers, 1974 January-Nov, 1975 January (Box 31, Folder 109-110)
        - Newsclippings and releases re: Chilean Health Workers, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 111)
      - Environmental Health Section: background material, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 112)
      - Fund Raising Committee: correspondence, guidelines and print material, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 113)
      - Medical Care Section
        - Correspondence, newsletters and list of members, 1965-1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 114)
        - Abstracts of contributed papers, 1976 October 18-21 (Box 31, Folder 115)
      - Membership Committee: list and correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 31, Folder 116)
      - Nominating Committee: minutes, correspondence and lists, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 117)
      - Occupational Health and Safety Council
        - Background material, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 118)
        - Correspondence, 1970-1973, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 119)
        - Suggested membership list and background material, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 120)
        - List of functions, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 121)
      - Occupational Health and Safety Section
        - Correspondence and background material, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 122)
        - Lists of committee members, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 123)
        - Correspondence re: program committee, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 124)
        - Agenda, program and abstracts for annual meeting, 1972 November (Box 32, Folder 125)
        - Correspondence, member lists and background material, 1973 January-April (Box 32, Folder 126)
        - Correspondence, 1973 May-August (Box 32, Folder 127)
        - Correspondence and related material re: occupational health issues in Congress, 1973, undated (Box 32, Folder 128)
        - Correspondence and background material, 1973 September-Dec, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 129)
        - Agenda, correspondence and report, 1973 September 24 (Box 32, Folder 130)
        - Correspondence, reports and related material, 1974, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 131)
      - Program Development Board: memorandum and minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 132)
      - Program Planning Committee
        - Report and general material re: annual meeting, 1974 January 7-8 (Box 32, Folder 133)
        - Outline, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 134)
      - Resolutions Committee: report, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 135)
      - Task Force, Health Considerations of a National Energy Policy: correspondence and background material, 1973 February (Box 33, Folder 136)
  - District of Columbia Department of Public Health, Public Health Advisory Council
    - General Papers
      - Correspondence and memoranda re: council members, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 137)
      - Memoranda, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 138)
      - Minutes and agendas, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 139)
      - Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 33, Folder 140)
      - Committee lists, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 141)
      - Organization chart and member list, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 142)
      - Annual report, financial papers and organization chart of District of Columbia General Hospital, 1966-1969 (Box 33, Folder 143)
      - Memoranda, 1967 January-June (Box 33, Folder 144)
      - Program, speech text and notes re: District of Columbia General Hospital workshop, 1967 May 26-27 (Box 33, Folder 145)
      - Memoranda, 1967 July-December (Box 33, Folder 146)
      - Correspondence re: Ad Hoc Committee on Committees, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 147)
      - Correspondence, minutes and member list re: Ad Hoc Committee on District of Columbia General Hospital, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 148)
      - Newsclippings re: District of Columbia General Hospital, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 149)
      - Memoranda re: Ad Hoc Committee on Comprehensive Health Planning, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 150)
      - Minutes and agendas, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 151)
      - Newsclippings, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 152)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 153)
    - Committees
      - Disease Control: memoranda, 1967 June (Box 33, Folder 154)
      - Environmental Health: report, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 155)
      - Maternal and Child Health: correspondence and memoranda, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 156)
      - Medical Care and Hospitals
        - General papers
          - Background material re: Medicaid legislation, 1963-1965 (Box 33, Folder 157)
          - Correspondence and minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 158)
          - Background material re: enabling Medicaid legislation, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 159)
          - Minutes and agenda, 1966 February-April (Box 34, Folder 160)
          - Minutes, agenda and memoranda, 1966 May-December (Box 34, Folder 161)
          - Organization chart, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 162)
          - Historical material re: Medicaid Plan for District of Columbia, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 163)
          - Memoranda, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 164)
        - Subcommittees
          - Allied Health Services: correspondence and minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 165)
          - Dental Services: correspondence and minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 166)
          - Eligibility Standards: correspondence, minutes and reports, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 167)
          - Hospitals and Extended Care Facilities
            - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 168)
            - Agenda and minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 169)
            - Member list and objectives, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 170)